game.net 2003-04-17

# GAME

## GAME Privacy Policy

### Table of Contents

  * Introduction
  * Third Party Sites
  * What personal information is collected?
    * GAME E-Commerce (Online Shopping)
    * Online Gaming (GAME.NET Multiplayer)
    * GAME Reward Card
  * Cookies
  * What happens to the information provided?
  * Where is the information held?
  * Opt-out Provision
  * Safeguarding Your Personal Information
  * Reviewing and Managing Your Information, Requesting Removal from Mailing Lists and Deactivating Your Accounts

### Introduction

GAME GROUP and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate-wide Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide online. All personal information relating to visitors, members, subscribers, Reward Card Holders or customers, using websites owned and operated by The GAME Group is held in accordance with The Data Protection Act 1998.

This privacy policy applies to the following web sites operated by The GAME Group:

  * game.uk.com 
  * game.net 
  * barrysworld.com 

In addition, The GAME Group owns several other domain names that point to the web sites listed above, and we will from time to time add new sites that may or may not be listed above. Please note that this policy applies only to sites maintained by GAME Group or its subsidiaries, and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organisations to which we link. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by The GAME Group online, not offline.

### Third Party Sites

If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the GAME-owned site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as The GAME Group. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to a GAME site, you should consult that site's privacy policy before providing any personal information.

### What personal information is collected?

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. GAME only collects personal information from our online visitors on a voluntary basis and only for;

  1. ordering products from us online, 
  2. competitions (registration or claiming a prize), 
  3. applying for a GAME Reward Card online, 
  4. registration for membership on our sites, 
  5. marketing surveys and email campaigns, 
  6. registration for newsletters, 
  7. registration for games or special game-specific event participation, or 
  8. when you request services from third party service providers on our site. 

Information collected may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address and birth date. We do not require personal information to obtain access to any of our sites; however, you will not be able to access areas that require registration.

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfil your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

Specific personal information may be required when transacting with three GAME services; e-commerce, online gaming and Reward Card:

_GAME E-commerce (online shopping)_

In addition to ensuring that we will only use the information that we collect about you lawfully (in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998).

We collect information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process your order and second, to provide you with the best possible service.

We will not email you in the future, other than for messages necessary for the maintenance of your membership or subscription, unless you have given us your consent.

We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing e-mail from us.

The type of information we collect about you includes:

  * your name 
  * your address 
  * e-mail address 
  * phone number 
  * credit/ debit card details 
  * order history and profile 

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by e-mailing us at [customerservices@game.uk.com](mailto:customerservices@game.uk.com). If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.

The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law and the Which? Web Trader Code.

If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.

We may use technology to track the patterns of behavior of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" (click here for more information on cookies) which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.

_Online Gaming (GAME.NET Multiplayer)_

In order to subscribe to GAME.NET Multiplayer (to play on game servers, use hosting etc.), you will need to be a Member of the GAME.NET Multiplayer service first.

As a member, the kind of information we collect about you would be:

  * your name 
  * your address 
  * e-mail address 
  * ICQ or Instant Messenger number (optional) 

As a subscriber, there may be the need to collect or use additional information about you such as: 

  * credit/ debit card details 
  * GAME Reward card details 

We collect information about you for two reasons: firstly, to process your subscription and second, in order to communicate service information to you. In order to join GAME.NET Multiplayer you must have a valid e-mail address. We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent.

We will give you the chance to refuse any marketing e-mail from us.

We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

You have the option to include your e-mail address, username and ICQ number (if supplied) in our Members Directory. This directory information is publicly available, and inclusion in the Directory is on an ''opt-in'' basis.

There is a further option to make more information about yourself publicly available by joining the GAME.NET Multiplayer Players Directory. In order to include your information in the Players Directory, you will have to opt-in to the Members Directory first.

_Online Forums, Chat, IRC and Profiles._

You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online forums or in creating user "profiles" when you play games on our sites or use chat rooms or IRC. Information that you disclose in chat rooms or in "profile" information is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality in either place. Please see our Terms & Conditions on this point and for other guidelines about posting content on our web sites.

You can check and amend information we hold about you by accessing your membership details in the GAME.NET Multiplayer Membership Section (requires log-in).

### GAME Reward Card

If you agree on application for a GAME Reward Card (either online or in-store), GAME may make the personal data provided by the cardholder available to associated companies to inform the cardholder about products and services. If, at any time, the cardholder does not wish their details to be made available, they should inform GAME in writing. (See ''Opt Out Provision'' below)

It is the responsibility of the cardholder to notify GAME, either through your local store (your nearest store can be found [here](http://www.game.uk.com/storesearch.asp)), online at <https://www.game.uk.com/reward/> or via Customer Services (tel: (00 44) 0870 750 2743) if the cardholders details are incorrect or change. For training purposes, any calls made to Customer Services may be monitored.

### What about cookies?

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser. On revisiting this site our computer servers will recognise the cookie, giving us information about your last visit. For example, certain of our sites use cookies or other methods to monitor website usage. We collect information on what games are played, and how much time is spent playing the games. We may link cookie information to personal information.

Most browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so.

### What happens to the information provided?

GAME Group does not share or disclose personal information other than as set forth in this policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act (1998), provided however, that in the event of a merger, acquisition, or the unlikely event of bankruptcy, management of GAME Group's customer information may be transferred to its successor or assign.

Members may register for other services from our site(s). If you opt in to any of these services, we may collect additional information requested by a service provider and pass this information, together with all other registration information (including personal information), to that service provider. Use of your information by a service provider will be governed by that service provider's terms of service and privacy policy. We may also retain any additional information collected for use in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Participation in these other related services is optional and is not required to play games on BarrysWorld.com, or participate in any of our other web sites.

We may use survey information in marketing surveys to select and direct advertising that is more likely to be of interest to a particular member. This information may be transmitted to an ad server owned by the advertising company to match members with ads that they are more likely to be interested in. However, we do not disclose any member's personal information to our advertisers without the member's consent. Participation in member surveys is entirely optional. We may share aggregate consumer data (which does not contain personal information) with the advertising companies.

Finally, we may use your personal information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs.

To enforce legal rights and the law, or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary to address potential or actual injury or interference with our rights, property, operations, users or others who may be harmed or may suffer loss or damage, we may also disclose personal information to the appropriate civil or legal authorities.

### Where is the information held?

GAME Group stores your data in the United Kingdom. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by GAME Group companies within the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.

### Opt-out Provision

When we first collect information about you, we will offer you the opportunity to opt-out of having your personal information shared with parties outside of The GAME Group of companies or its subsidiaries (except to the extent required by law, court order, or as requested by other government or legal agencies). In addition, if you do not want The GAME Group of companies to send you e-mail or postal mail about our products and services, you can opt out at the time of registration or information collection. If, at a later date, you choose to have your name removed from our mailing list, you can do so by contacting GAME Customer Services by e-mail at [customerservices@game.uk.com](mailto:customerservices@game.uk.com), by telephone; (tel: (00 44) 0870 750 2743), or in writing. You may also click the unsubscribe link on our email offers and newsletters.

### Safeguarding Your Personal Information

We will only collect and use personal information in accordance with this privacy policy to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and we will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity, accuracy and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, we will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom we transfer any personal information will provide sufficient protection of that information.

### Reviewing and Managing Your Information, Requesting Removal from Mailing Lists and Deactivating Your Accounts 

If for any reason you are concerned that the personal information maintained by The GAME Group is not correct, or should you wish to have your account(s) deactivated or be removed from any of our mailing lists, please contact Customer Services or use the appropriate unsubscribe links in newsletters etc. In the case of personal information held in connection with your GAME Reward Card, you can review and amend your personal details at any time by logging on to your account at http://www.game.uk.com/reward. You can also contact our Customer Services team and we will be happy to review, update or remove information as appropriate. We may still retain your information in our files however, to resolve disputes, enforce our user agreement, and due to technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of our websites.

By using this site, you signify your assent to the GAME Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any GAME Group site. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check the policy each time you use our web site to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our privacy policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Also, if there is a substantive change in the way that we use your personal information, we will notify you via e-mail of the relevant changes. If you choose to opt-out of our changed practice, our e-mail will contain instructions on how to opt-out. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Online Privacy Policy.

This policy was last amended on 16th October 2002.
